(Girl dressed as a Witch:)- It's a great party.
- Thank you.
(Witch:)The monster foods, they're really fun.
(Stuart:)Oh, yes, thank you.
I like to think of fun things like that...
(Stuart:)...because I'm fun,
I'm not clinically depressed at all.
(Amy:)Sheldon, get in here.
I should have picked hickey.
(Stuart:)Hey, look at you guys!
I'm Raggedy Anne and he's Raggedy C-3P0.
(Sheldon:)It was a compromise. I lost.
(Raj:)Can you believe Stuart's walking around
taking credit for this party?
(Raj:)- Who cares?
- What do you mean, who cares?
Look what I pulled off here.
The DJ's on fire...
(Raj:)...there's a TARDIS photo booth
in the back...
(Raj:)...oh, my God, the food.
Stuart wanted Kraft Draculoni and Cheese.